[Music]
[音乐]
我将向您展示如何制作
I'm going to show you how to make a
情人卡，在这种情况下是
图飞跃而图是
I'm going to show you how to make a
Valentine card which in this case is a
会抱着几个心
所以这是基于平行四边形
Valentine card which in this case is a
figure leaping up and the the figure is
这是教程五，有几个
我到这里的其他例子中
figure leaping up and the the figure is
going to be holding a couple of hearts
在我开始之前告诉你
另一个拿着球或其他东西
going to be holding a couple of hearts
so this is based on the parallelogram
但是我们要让它成为一颗心
其实你可以玩这个，你可以
so this is based on the parallelogram
which is tutorial five there's a couple
有一个以上的数字，所以这是
两个数字的另一个例子是
which is tutorial five there's a couple
of other examples I've got here I'll
仍然基于的基本原理
我觉得这个平行四边形很
of other examples I've got here I'll
just show you before I start here's
真正令人愉悦的是从基本卡开始
这是完全折痕的基础，
just show you before I start here's
another one holding a ball or something
然后这是我们想要的另一块
适合与背景融合
another one holding a ball or something
but we're going to make it a heart and
我会做一个很小的
这样的平行四边形在这里
but we're going to make it a heart and
actually you can play with this you can
折叠在一端的标签中，然后我们
来像这样的东西
actually you can play with this you can
have more than one figure so here's
折起然后短距离
这样，然后我们将有一个
have more than one figure so here's
another example of two figures it's the
标签在另一端，所以这是标准的
平行四边形
another example of two figures it's the
same basic principle it's still based on
对，然后加强这些
折痕，所以一切都很好
same basic principle it's still based on
the parallelogram I find this quite
这个的关键是
平行四边形长边短边当
the parallelogram I find this quite
pleasing really start with a base card
底座是平的，平行四边形是
平，那里将有
pleasing really start with a base card
here's the base thoroughly creased and
这里和这里的两个小三角形和
这里和这里这是四肢
here's the base thoroughly creased and
then here's another piece we want it to
适合，所以这是与
三个折痕，然后在这里，我们
then here's another piece we want it to
fit in to blend in with the background
不会像那样折叠它，我们会做
当我们在这边也一样
fit in to blend in with the background
I'm just going to make quite a small
打开，我们有这四个小
三角形，所以我们只需确保
I'm just going to make quite a small
parallelogram like this piece here so
那真的是牧师，所以
所有动作真的
parallelogram like this piece here so
fold in a tab on one end and then we
甜美地被卡住
一起
fold in a tab on one end and then we
come along something like that put a
现在，所有平行四边形都有
长边卡在短距离内
come along something like that put a
crease in it and then a short distance
脊椎，你有一个短边
距离很远
crease in it and then a short distance
like that and then we're going to have a
脊椎，所以我拿铅笔，我会
只是在这里标记短边
like that and then we're going to have a
tab on the other end so this is standard
弄皱的谎言就在那里，因为
当基地
tab on the other end so this is standard
parallelogram
是平的，我们不需要测量
另一端，所以我在上面放胶水
right and then just reinforce these
那是长的一面
平行四边形平行于
right and then just reinforce these
creases so it all works really well so
脊柱，离它不远
将此面朝下粘贴，这样就可以
the key to this one is this is the
平放下来实际上就是这样
圆形，因此将其折叠成封闭状态
the key to this one is this is the
parallelogram long side short side when
位置关闭它找到的基地
它想要坚持，然后我们打开它
parallelogram long side short side when
the base is flat the parallelogram is
向上，当底座是
平这里我们有这四个小
the base is flat the parallelogram is
flat and there's there are going to have
三角形，这就是我们可以坚持的地方
四肢，所以我会做一个系列
flat and there's there are going to have
two little triangles here and here and
这块的四肢可以是
棘手的是因为它们关闭时
two little triangles here and here and
here and here which is what the limbs
您朝着不同的方向移动
可能需要玩转和量身定制
here and here which is what the limbs
fit onto so here's the piece with the
这些，以便在关闭时不会
像这只手，你会看到有一点
fit onto so here's the piece with the
three creases and then it's here we
那里的弯曲看起来
某些地方被它相对
three creases and then it's here we
won't fold it in like that and we'll do
页面关闭时的书脊或书脊
所以你可能需要玩
won't fold it in like that and we'll do
the same on this side as well when we
这些找到适合你的
在这个例子中，四肢处于
the same on this side as well when we
open that up we've got these four little
不同的形式，所以这个就像你
关闭它，您可以看到这条腿的样子
open that up we've got these four little
triangles and so we just make sure
去有被绊倒的危险
针对该页面，但可以，并且
triangles and so we just make sure
that's all really thoroughly priest so
已经很好地解决了，所以我只是
从这四个四肢，所以我们去
that's all really thoroughly priest so
that all moves really
我要弯曲的腿
这些在这种情况下非常粗糙
that all moves really
sweetly when it comes to being stuck
所以这是一条腿，让我们做一点
更短，我们可以坚持下去
sweetly when it comes to being stuck
together
现在我在上面放一些胶水
三角形把腿伸进去，我会
together
now with all parallelograms you have a
只要检查一下是否确实有效
当页面关闭时，一个人的摇摆
now with all parallelograms you have a
long side stuck over a short distance to
围绕页面，以便一个
似乎还可以，但是如果这
long side stuck over a short distance to
the spine and you've got a short side
只是被困在这里
认为我们可能会遇到麻烦，所以我
the spine and you've got a short side
which is stuck down a long distance from
要改变顶部的形状
腿，这样你就可以把它放下来
which is stuck down a long distance from
the spine so I get the pencil and I'll
所以我要贴在那个角落
现在我要在上面放一些胶水
the spine so I get the pencil and I'll
just mark the short side here where the
试试这个，这样你就可以看到
其实不是我想做的
just mark the short side here where the
crease lies so that's there and because
我们将不得不改变这一点
离开并开始，所以这是腿
crease lies so that's there and because
the whole thing goes flat when the base
没有像那样的工作
而且那个没有用，所以让我们
the whole thing goes flat when the base
is flat we don't need to measure the
看看这些我已经调整了
多一点，多一点胶
is flat we don't need to measure the
other end so I put glue on there
回到那里再试一次
以这个角度出来是正确的
that's the long side of the
这次接近页面，是的，所以
那是四条腿，现在我们想要一个
that's the long side of the
parallelogram stuck down parallel to the
两臂，让我们来
这样的事情我们真的不需要
parallelogram stuck down parallel to the
spine and just a short distance from it
太担心手了
因为它会拿着一些
spine and just a short distance from it
stick this side down so that should go
心，那只是
如果你看这些而他们卡住了
stick this side down so that should go
flat down just actually do it this way
在小的一面，这件实际上是
相对页面旋转，因此非常
flat down just actually do it this way
round so folding it into its closed
实际上几乎没有机会
那里的问题
round so folding it into its closed
position close the base it finds where
这是那些坚持到这两个
长边的三角形
position close the base it finds where
it wants to stick and then we open that
页面关闭，他们实际上翻转了
那就是问题开始出现的地方
it wants to stick and then we open that
up and it goes flat when the base is
我们的肢体还可以，现在我们将
再做一次，我会尽力做到的
up and it goes flat when the base is
flat here we have these four little
像我这样有点角度
认为从那看来似乎
flat here we have these four little
triangles and that's where we can stick
好的，这一个
这样的东西
triangles and that's where we can stick
the limbs on so I'll just make a series
也许我只是尝试一下
将其关闭，看起来很好
the limbs on so I'll just make a series
of limbs from this piece these can be
关于它不是很高兴，但
还不错，然后我们需要一个头
of limbs from this piece these can be
tricky because as it closes they all
我会做一些真正基本的事情
这次不，我要改变它
tricky because as it closes they all
move in in different directions you
并把它放在这边，因为我们知道
这边是安全的，它旋转
move in in different directions you
might need to play around and tailor
方式而不是翻转，所以我们知道
贴在那一边的头会
might need to play around and tailor
these so that as it closes they don't
好的，事实上，当您开始制作
你自己的设计，你可能会做所有
these so that as it closes they don't
like this hand you can see there's a bit
这些合二为一
只是折痕的一部分
like this hand you can see there's a bit
of a bend there it looks as though at
是的，你可以看到那是
在这种情况下，我已经做到了
of a bend there it looks as though at
some points it's snagged against the
折痕和腿是一个
折痕，但要做到这一点
some points it's snagged against the
page or the spine as the page is closed
经历一些假的车辙
尝试直到我知道所有角度为止
page or the spine as the page is closed
so you might need to play around with
然后现在这工作正常，所以现在
我们可以添加心，所以这一个
so you might need to play around with
these to find the ones that work for you
心脏在哪里并不重要
因为我们知道它会安全地移动
these to find the ones that work for you
in this example the limbs are in a
那里有一个工作正常
您必须在这里小心，因为
in this example the limbs are in a
different formation so this one as you
我们必须看看它的趋势
抓住，你可以看到它趋向于
different formation so this one as you
close it you can see the way this leg is
紧扣在底部，而顶部
有点在这里是安全的地方
close it you can see the way this leg is
going it is in danger of snagging
让我们把它粘在那里
当我们关闭它时，是的，它正在工作
going it is in danger of snagging
against that page but it's okay and it
在您自己的设计中当然不是
你可能会这么粗暴
against that page but it's okay and it
has been worked out nicely so I'll just
甚至把自己的照片放在这里，你
可以把各种各样的东西放在这里
has been worked out nicely so I'll just
make four four limbs from this so we go
有更多设计余地
工作，但这是基本机制
make four four limbs from this so we go
with a bent leg I'm just going to make
那就是心灵的带来者
情人卡
with a bent leg I'm just going to make
these quite crudely in this case
您
[音乐]
so here's a leg let's make it a bit